<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial: Create a personal webpage in RStudio using R/blogdown on Boryana Koseva, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>/tutorials/blogdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial: Create a personal webpage in RStudio using R/blogdown on Boryana Koseva, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Boryana S. Koseva &amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tutorials/blogdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Instructions for Mac OS</title>
      <link>/tutorials/blogdown/software_mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorials/blogdown/software_mac/</guid>
      <description>On a Mac, you will need the following software installed and updated to the most recent versions available:
Note: if installing these software for the first time, please do them in the order in which they are listed.
 R RStudio Homebrew
To check if you have Homebrew installed on your computer, open a Terminal window (Applications ➡️ Utilities ➡️ Terminal), and type the following at the prompt:
brew update  If the command returns a bash: brew: command not found, brew is not installed on your computer, and you can install it by typing the following command into terminal:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Instructions for Windows</title>
      <link>/tutorials/blogdown/software_windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorials/blogdown/software_windows/</guid>
      <description>On a Windows, you will need the following software installed and updated to the most recent versions available:
Note: if installing these software for the first time, please do them in the order in which they are listed.
 R Rtools
Download and install the recommended version of the software. Git Bash
Use the default settings during installation. RStudio blogdown
To install blogdown and its dependencies, open RStudio and type the following into the console:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background</title>
      <link>/tutorials/blogdown/concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorials/blogdown/concepts/</guid>
      <description>Concepts you will need to be familiar with during the workshop:
 Static webpage Hugo: Static webpage generator Markdown/R markdown blogdown git/version control repo  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>